insidetexas.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy - Inside Texas | Inside Texas

Thank you for visiting InsideTexas.com.

We are committed to your privacy and provide the following Privacy Policy that explains how we strive to protect your personally identifiable data. Our goal is to bring you current and up-to-date information about the sports programs at The University of Texas, tailored to your individual interest and needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.

YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE AND/OR REGISTRATION WITH InsideTexas WILL CONSTITUTE YOUR AGREEMENT WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

In addition, please read our Terms of Use Agreement as your use of InsideTexas.com website and/or service(s) constitutes agreement to the terms as explained in the Agreement.

This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation, offline and online sites that are linked to and from our website.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. Continued access of this website and/or service(s) by you will constitute youracceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

InsideTexas does not collect personal information without your specific knowledge and consent.

For instance, when you register for any portion of InsideTexas’s services, make a purchase, subscribe to our affiliated publication(s), enter a sweepstakes or contest, or complete a survey, you are asked to provide, among other things, information like your e-Mail address, name, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about interest in our services, products, and programs. Optional demographic information may also be requested. The more information you provide, the better we are able to customize our services to suit your needs and preferences.

InsideTexas uses the information you supply to provide you with the services that you request. For example, if you subscribe to any of our affiliated publications, we may use your e-Mail address to send you the publication. Similarly, if you enter one of our contests or sweepstakes, we will use the information provided to notify you if you win. We may also use the information supplied to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer to you.

## ‘COOKIES’

In addition, when you use InsideTexas’s website and/or service(s), we may also automatically collect information, (‘Cookies’), about you or your computer, including without limitation, the internet address that you just came from, the internet address that you go to next, the internet address that referred you, the type of browser software you are using, the domain name of your Internet Service provider, and your Internet Protocol address. This information is collected and used in the aggregate for, among other things, measuring site performance and use.

‘Cookies’ on InsideTexas simply help you get around the site faster, and are used to enable functions such as showing whether or not a thread or forum you are viewing has new posts since your last visit, or to automatically log you back in when you return to the site after being away for a while.

For example, when you Register, you will be given the option to ‘Automatically login’ when you return to the site. This will save your username and password in a ‘cookie,’ stored on your computer. If you do not check the ‘Auto LogIn,’ we clear them as you exit.

Unlike most sites, we do not collect cookies for ‘permission based marketing’ or give any personal information to anyone. Our advertisers do not have any access to your information or ‘cookies.’ We will not sell any ad to any advertiser who requires that we share cookies or tracking information.

## RESTRICTIONS ON USE OF INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU

InsideTexas will not sell or share your information, or allow access to our database to non related third parties. However, affiliated companies, (such as ESPN), that provide us goods or services, such as a subscription to an ESPN magazine, or the technical maintenance of our website, are granted limited access to provide the services you have requested. These companies however, also agree to guard your privacy and to never sell any data obtained through us to anyone for any reason.

## USERS UNDER 17 YEARS OLD

While content on InsideTexas is meant to be viewed by sports fans of all ages, we ask that fans under age 17 not post on the forums, provide any personal information to us, or to any third party on our message boards or chat rooms. Minors under the age of 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases or registering with InsideTexas.

## PRIVACY POLICY COORDINATOR

If you have any questions or comments about any aspect of this Privacy Policy, then please feel free to contact us at the address below:

Inside Texas  
P.O. Box 9192  
Austin, TX 78766

Questions about our privacy policy may be directed to: [HELP@InsideTexas.com](mailto:HELP@InsideTexas.com)
